[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "VBZ", "VBN", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 34, "question": "How do you feel?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 35, "answer": "We were blindsided by everything that has happened past week and a half.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBD", "VBN", "DT", ":", "RB", "DT", "RB", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 36, "question": "I mean, what rumors had you heard prior to this week?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "WP", "NNS", "VBD", "PRP", "VBN", "RB", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 37, "answer": "We officially had heard some -- just a little gossip around town, some community, you know, gossip, as every community has.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 40, "question": "Why do you think that was?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 41, "answer": "I'm not for sure.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["summer", "summer", "2011"]}, "docId": "111116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBD", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "CD", ",", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", ":", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 46, "question": "And when did that happen?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "VBD", "IN", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 47, "answer": "That was this summer, this past summer, 2011, the golf tournament raise -- the fund-raiser that they have.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 49, "question": "Is that right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 50, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "NN", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 51, "question": "Who was that, from the Second Mile charity?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "IN", ",", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 52, "answer": "I'm not at liberty to say.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Second Mile"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["2008"]}, "docId": "111116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBG", "TO", "DT", "NNS", "CC", "VBG", "TO", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "IN", "CD", ",", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 56, "question": "Do you now believe that at the time you were told there was nothing to worry about that actually they knew that the charity was well aware of what was going on?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "RB", "VBD", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "RB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "WP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 57, "answer": "I believe, according to the media and according to the grand jury, it says that in 2008, the Second Mile put him, you know, he stepped down and he was not allowed to be involved in the activities with children.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", ":", "IN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "NN", "WDT", "MD", "VB", "RP", "CC", "VB", "DT", "NN", "CC", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 61, "question": "What would you do about this, if anything?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", ",", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 62, "answer": "We are hoping to -- in the community to recover, we are hoping to find someone that will step up and be a leader and, you know, help our community.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "VB", "RP", "CC", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 73, "question": "What would you describe the current mood of the students as?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 74, "answer": "We're looking for someone in our community to step up and be a leader.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "POS", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 90, "question": "From a legal perspective, I would imagine that's a dangerous position to be adopted right now, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "POS", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "RB", "RB", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 91, "answer": "Well, I think the prosecutor's office is definitely looking at all of the evidence.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 101, "question": "Are you a pedophile?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 102, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 104, "question": "Am I sexually to underage boys?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 105, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "IN", "RB", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 113, "question": "How ill-advised was that interview, do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBD", "IN", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 114, "answer": "RIEL: Well, I'll say this, that it's highly unusual for a defense attorney to let his client be interviewed in that fashion, and for exactly the reason we just saw.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "NN", "IN", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 122, "question": "Is that -- is that unhelpful to the legal process, having him convicted in the court of popular opinion?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", ":", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBG", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 123, "answer": "Well, I think that our system is innocent until proven.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 130, "question": "What is your view of had his legal position here, in terms of potentially being involved in a cover-up from all that you've seen and read and heard?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "VBD", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "RB", ",", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "RB", "VBG", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "DT", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "CC", "VB", "CC", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 131, "answer": "Well, I think -- I'm not really prepared to discuss whether I think he was involved in a cover-up.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "CD", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "NN", "IN", "CC", "NNS", "IN", "DT", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", ":", "NN", "POS", "NN", "PRP", "IN", "NN", ",", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 151, "question": "And from all of your experience in these kind of cases, when you heard Jerry Sandusky talking, what did your gut feel tell you about the kind of language that he was using and his behavioral pattern?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "DT", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "NN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "CC", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 152, "answer": "Well, as we mentioned before, the fact that it took him a while to answer that one question, the way he meandered around some other questions, his referring to horsing around and things like that -- it didn't strike me as a very good defensive posture -- let's put it that way, coming from a lawyer.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jerry Sandusky"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["NPT"]}, "docId": "111116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "RB", "VBP", "JJ", "NNS", "CC", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 180, "question": "What is your reaction to that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 181, "answer": "While this kind of allegation is quite interesting from a person who is from a country that already possess nuclear weapons and is a renegade country in the eye of NPT.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["IAEA"]}, "docId": "111116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "VBP", "CD", "NNS", "VBG", "IN", "EX", "."], "qSentId": 185, "question": "If as you say, it's all completely peaceful and above- board, why don't you just let everybody come have a look and inspect them in the peace and tranquility that you talk of?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "CC", "JJ", "NN", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "NN", "NN", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "CC", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 186, "answer": "Well, the cameras of IAEA are 24 hours working over there.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 201, "question": "Do you believe in it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 202, "answer": "Holocaust is a historical matter.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Sarkozy", "Obama"], "LOCATION": ["Iran", "Iran"]}, "docId": "111116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJS", "NN", "NNS", "RB", "VBP", "VBG", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NN", "VBZ", "VBG", "RP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 211, "question": "Our view is that, why not like centuries Muslims, Christians and Jews could live together in such beautiful piece of land which is called Palestine?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", ",", "WRB", "RB", "IN", "NNS", "NNP", ",", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "MD", "VB", "RP", "IN", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "VBN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 212, "answer": "Do you feel threatened in Iran in the sense that most world leaders now are being openly hostile towards Iran, whether it's President Sarkozy, President Obama, President Medvedev -- I mean, everyone is cueing up to say you are a dangerous country.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "EX", "VBP", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 215, "question": "So, the kind of obvious question to me, is if you're not developing nuclear weapons, which you are saying other countries have, Israel to Pakistan and certainly America, many other countries have nuclear weapons, why wouldn't Iran want to have a nuclear weapon to defend itself?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "PRP", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", ",", "NNP", "TO", "NNP", "CC", "RB", "NNP", ",", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "WRB", "MD", "RB", "NNP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 216, "answer": "Well, there are two reasons.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Israel", "Pakistan", "America", "Iran"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["United States"]}, "docId": "111116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "NN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "CC", "NN", "CC", "NN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNPS", "."], "qSentId": 229, "question": "How do you view military action against you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 230, "answer": "Well, I mean, before assessing these claims on the military and defense and security basis, I think this is a good distraction from the basic problems in the United States.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "111116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "CC", "JJ", "NN", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 248, "question": "What was your reaction?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 249, "answer": "Total and complete nonsense, Piers.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "POS", "RB", "WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 268, "question": "What is the right way to deal with Iran, if they're going to flagrantly ignore any form of international community opinion on this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 269, "answer": "Well, I think that's exactly what's going on.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Iran"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "111116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 297, "question": "Are you frustrated that you are still lagging in the polls when the credentials that you seem to offer at this very challenging time for America, particularly on the international stage, seem so much more impressive than many of your rivals?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "WRB", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "RB", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "RBR", "JJ", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 298, "answer": "Well, we're still in the preseason, Piers.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 365, "question": "As things stand, he's going to walk it, isn't he?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NNS", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 366, "answer": "He has name recognition.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "PRP", ",", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 405, "question": "Are they a force for good or catastrophe in your campaign?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 406, "answer": "Watch it, dad.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}, "docId": "111116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "NNP", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 424, "question": "And what can he do about it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 425, "answer": "Well, he hasn't had a chance to have America see him yet.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 432, "question": "What is the secret Jon Huntsman like?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 433, "answer": "Careful.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jon Huntsman"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 442, "question": "Is he boring?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 443, "answer": "Not at all.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 451, "question": "What is the one thing that is going to drive you past Mitt Romney?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "CD", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "JJ", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 452, "answer": "New Hampshire loves an underdog.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mitt Romney"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ":", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 466, "question": "Do you disagree?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 467, "answer": "I -- it wouldn't be for me to comment.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 468, "question": "But who had the worst haircut, in your opinion?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBD", "DT", "JJS", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 469, "answer": "We think our dad had the best haircut.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 474, "question": "Jon, do you worry that your daughters are going to land you -- you're going to wake up one morning and all hell has broken loose on Twitter?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RP", "CD", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 475, "answer": "Piers, I don't have a choice.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "DT", "IN", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 494, "question": "Or is it just whatever goes through your minds?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 495, "answer": "IVINGSTON: Look, we're really doing this for a very serious reason.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "CC", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 506, "question": "Have you got any more shocking surprises for us?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "RBR", "VBG", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 507, "answer": "I guess you'll just have to wait and see.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 524, "question": "What are you worth?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 525, "answer": "I don't know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]